Challenge is on.
He's the interschool champion.
Oof!
Good job.
Your brother is not bad.
I just won.
He's good with a racket.
Shame about his background.
Explains his attitude, though.
-What'd you say?
-You heard me.
-Say it again.
-Hey!
-Why is he so rude?
-Okay. Okay.
There are those who are good at games.
And those who complain.
Huh. Speaker's son?
-He started it.
-Here's an idea.
Before you talk nonsense,
count to ten first.
Don't embarrass your family.
Huh?
You're afraid of that guy?
What do you mean?
He's annoyed me for ages.
Anyway, I'll climb higher than him.
He doesn't scare me.
He had a point.
Other people don't see me
as part of the Hsueh family.
Don't talk like that.
Dad'll see how great you are one day.
Then the two of us will do great things.
Like what?
Get your racket out. I'll beat you.
Oh! You wanna get smashed, huh?
I think I got a better plan.
THE FIXERS
BACKSTABBER
HOWIE, MISSED CALL
ONE NEW VOICEMAIL
Dad, get back here.
We're in danger.
Police, how can I help you?
I wanna report a crime.
The boy's innocent.
-He doesn't know anything.
-Give me the right answer.
And I assure you,
we'll leave you to your day.
Police, open up.
Everything all right?
We've had complaints about the noise.
Watch what you say.
Or your son gets hurt.
If someone's in there, open the door now.
All right.
-Hi.
-Neighbors reported a commotion.
A commotion?
I sell products livestream.
I might have got a bit excited.
-Can I take a look?
-Uh, everything's all right.
-Don't trouble yourself, okay?
-I'll be off now.
-Just tell me when the goods get here.
-Mmm. Right.
-All right?
-Everything's fine.
-Keep the noise down.
-Okay, thanks.
Howie? Howie!
Howie, are you all right?
Oh, please don't scare me! Howie!
Please get up.
Answer me!
You're scaring me. Howie!
-Fuck.
-Honey, what do we do?
Tell me who they are.
Okay. Then I'll ring the police.
You can't call the cops.
Why can't I call them?
Tell me what you've been doing out there.
Legislator Chao Ming-cheng's
bribery case continues to escalate.
Ching He's Thackery Huang,
initially suspected of being a middleman,
now thought to be involved
in a number of cases,
according to the latest evidence
gathered by prosecutors Huang…
Now I want you to give me
a straight answer.
Tell me who these people are.
Once he's awake, we'll get out of here.
What if he can't wake up?
What if our son can't wake up?
You're holding onto so many secrets.
You're not young Gold's
bodyguard, are you?
We're partners.
In what, exactly?
We work for Ching He.
Ching He?
Mmm.
So you're back.
We haven't had a drink
together for a while.
Here.
Oh, wait, it's just you and me.
We shouldn't drink this.
So you've decided to help me
with the Primordial Files.
As Dad said, I'm a Hsueh.
Who better to help out?
And the reason I joined Ching He,
it was so I could help the Hsuehs one day.
I knew I could trust you.
I wish Dad was here.
This would make him so happy.
You're not doing this
just for Dad, are you?
It's about what you want.
I thought you went into all this
because Dad made you do it.
But you love the power.
Hmm.
Look at that bridge.
It connects the two sides of the city.
On one side is power and order.
On the other, opportunity and ambition.
Dad's belief is the two sides
shouldn't be opposed,
that they should coexist.
That's not what I think.
Coexistence is giving in.
In this world, it's the strong
who set the agenda.
The bridge should be blown up.
That's what I'd like to see.
No boundaries.
Everyone following one set agenda.
And I set that one agenda.
I hate relying on Dad too.
I hate being dependent.
I have my own view of the future.
I'll help. But promise me, will you?
What?
Don't touch Felix or Mina.
It sounds like there are some things
that Yeh Yueh Tong hasn't told you.
Okay, you got it.
Are you okay?
My son's life was saved.
But he hasn't woken up yet.
The doctor says
the next 48 hours are the most critical.
Thackery was arrested.
I saw it on a news report.
Hmm. There'll be a new leader.
Madam Fan wants to replace Thackery
as the head of Ching He.
So what happened?
Fan's father was the former leader.
Now she wants to reclaim
the position she thinks belongs to her.
This is for Thackery.
Is it too late to give it to him?
What is it?
Just before Zoe died…
she gave me this.
Did you open it?
I haven't.
But Zoe wanted me to hand this
to Thackery in person.
Give it to me. I'll give it to him.
He's been arrested.
How will you give it to him?
I'm going to visit him in jail.
Zoe said the things on this…
are about the Hsuehs.
I just found out the Hsueh family were
responsible for arresting him.
The card's contents could stop Madam Fan
from being Ching He's new leader.
Mmm.
Trust me.
When Howie wakes up.
I'll take him and his mother away.
Hmm.
Far away.
CHING HE TEMPLE
We've managed to detain Thackery.
And you were such a big help.
Without you, things wouldn't
have gone so smoothly.
It's time, I think,
for Ching He to embrace the new.
You fought valiantly for Ching He
through everything.
I promise you, I will bring
nothing but benefit to Ching He.
From now on,
with the Hsueh family as an ally,
Ching He will be more powerful.
If only Thackery would step down.
With Madam Fan as chair, however,
there still may be some variables.
With the Hsueh family's
assistance, we can certainly grow.
But you need to know
Ching He's neutrality is vital.
I must request that you honor it.
I didn't want to say it before,
but now you're on board,
that won't be an issue.
I heard there were two keys
in the possession of the leader.
Thackery has one of them.
So whereabouts is the other?
I look after it.
Well, are you willing to hand it over?
I can't hand it over right now.
We haven't had the inauguration.
It's not our way.
Sir Hong.
Since we've come this far,
we don't want any mishaps.
I understand.
Do you think he'll hand it over?
If he decides to help me,
I can only applaud his decision.
Sir Hong's family has been
with Ching He for generations.
Each newly appointed leader
needs his assistance,
if they want to get anything done.
That puts my mind at ease.
I heard there are two people
who are causing you trouble.
Who? Say.
Felix Chiang and Mina Shen.
Louis wanted me to get you to spare them.
But he didn't tell me
why you're after them.
So I guess I'm curious.
They know something
to do with an important client.
I had to scare the two of them off.
But, since Louis has asked,
I promise.
How could I turn him down?
I'm curious about Louis.
What role does he have to play?
If Thackery won't step down,
he could help us out there.
This is his condition in exchange.
I understand.
I appreciate that.
You're welcome, Mr. Mayor.
It's a pleasure working with you.
So, what is it you know?
Zoe's dead.
I have something she wanted to give you.
The contents were surprising.
So what's your plan from here?
It's to do with the Hsuehs.
You won't be getting it.
Are you going to betray us?
When I joined Ching He, I said,
"One day, this will help the Hsuehs."
Never thought it would be like this.
I need to tell you
I always knew who your family was.
So why did I let you join Ching He?
To get at the Hsueh clan.
You're not like your brother.
All this time,
your continued performance for Ching He
has never disappointed me.
Even now,
I can see
you're still the Louis who turned up
at my door all those years ago.
You sure of that?
My brother's made a tempting offer.
I'm a Hsueh at heart, you know.
If you'll step down,
I can guarantee your safety.
You don't have to bother.
I know my time's over.
I just hope Ching He can survive.
If I have to step down, I'll step down.
But if the Primordial Files are
controlled by the wrong individual,
the balance of the scales
will be disturbed.
And the genie won't go back in the bottle.
Let the next head of Ching He
worry about that.
What happens when
the Hsueh family find out about the video?
They must find out who else knows.
And do you think they'll be spared?
Since Tristan's taking an interest,
remember, keep it clean.
Anyone with knowledge
of the Hsueh family secret,
they cannot live, you hear me?
Yes, ma'am.
-You feeling better?
-Young Gold?
The doctor says it's not serious
and his brain's all right.
A little longer and they'll discharge him.
I'll see what I can arrange.
-I know the head of neurology here.
-Oh.
Why haven't you been
to our house for dinner lately?
Now, now. You be polite.
I will when you've recovered.
But the house isn't safe right now.
That won't happen again. Don't worry.
Uh…
Are you here for my husband?
Hasn't he told you he's quitting?
We're parting ways.
I can handle the rest.
Why are you here?
Have you seen Thackery?
He's retiring. Fan will take over.
Did he choose to step down?
It's not his choice to make.
And the footage. Did you give it to him?
You know about the video,
so you're in danger.
But Madame Fan's not in charge yet.
You need to go.
-Take your family and leave.
-So you didn't give him the footage?
And now you wanna help out.
Help the Hsueh family and Fan
take over Ching He.
This is not your concern.
You must leave here.
Do you appreciate how many have been hurt?
Huh?
Fuck, I trusted you like you're a brother.
Fuck!
This is for my son.
For Zoe and her daughter.
And Ben!
Did so many people have to suffer and die
just so you could be Ching He's chairman?
Fucking bastard.
Get away with your family.
Fuck.
-Where's your mom?
-She's gone out.
She's looking for food.
Oh.
Why are you reading?
Doesn't your head hurt?
When I'm discharged, I'll have exams.
I've failed you both.
I couldn't protect you and your mom.
Now, you should know,
if this happens again,
you just need to get out.
Run like the wind, okay?
Dad.
If it was you,
you would have protected Mom.
But I know you've got
important stuff to deal with right now.
-Has he gone?
-He has.
Hey.
Can you handle
how he's discharged tomorrow?
Then let's get out of here.
Did you and your partner have a fight?
Get out of here where?
And for how long?
It's one thing for the two of us,
but does our son have
to live in hiding as well?
Deal with this now.
You leave it any longer,
your hands will get worse,
and then where will you be?
We've known each other a long time.
I know every little piece of you.
And I know
that you're looking after
Chi's daughter.
And I'm so angry.
I'm so angry
that you've said nothing about it.
When Howie's discharged in a few days,
I'm gonna take him back
to my mother's place.
So, until then, you sort this out.
And then come home safe.
Do you hear me?
Don't worry, Dad.
Until you get back,
I'll look after your wife for you.
Oh, don't do that.
You sound just like your dad.
It's gonna be okay. Hang in there.
Hang in there, you hear me?
You and me. We'll finish it right here.
Bless me, please, Lord Guan,
so we can get out of this.
Deal with it.
All right.
Swamp Eel! It's been a while.
You're an old man now.
Why are you still running?
Is your boss around?
I'm here to ask for a favor.
A favor for who?
An old friend.
Thackery Huang.
Hmm.
How do you want me to help you?
We need to stop Fan taking over Ching He.
You gotta be joking.
You wanna drag San He into this mess?
If San He gets involved,
that's declaring war on the Hsueh clan.
As well as Yeh Yueh Tong.
Don't forget, It was you guys
who toppled Fan's father
and made Thackery chairman.
So if you now let Madame Fan take control,
you could be in trouble.
She's the kind of operator
that you don't wanna fuck with.
If we have to fight dirty.
then it's a whole other story.
ARCADE
Did Louis send you here?
No he didn't.
I wanted to see you.
We have a common enemy.
You and me, let's take out Fan.
-Why?
-Huh.
That fucker, she hurt my son.
At least you still have people to protect.
That's fine. It was a mistake to come.
Ben wouldn't want you avenging him.
I'll join you.
My partners know I won't let this rest.
At worst, when we see each other again,
they'll give me attitude.
We're here to see a patient.
-How many times do I tell you?
-You can't, unless you're family.
Since when was that a rule?
-Please be quiet.
-It's okay, I'll go.
Don't be like that.
You're treating us like debt collectors.
You look like debt collectors.
Debt collectors don't bring fruit!
-I can't let you in.
-How are you?
Uh, hello.
Don't worry, nurse, we know each other.
Smile, guys, you gave her
the wrong idea. Lighten up.
-Ma'am.
-Tell them to keep their voices down.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Uh… so you're here
and you brought a party?
Pond Loach has lots of things
he has to do, so he called me.
-For safety.
-Aah.
Where's the box?
-Oh.
-Idiot!.
-You were supposed to bring it inside!
-You shouldn't have.
Why do you eat tien-bu-la with
just blood pudding and deep-fried tofu?
When my parents passed away,
I had to live with my aunt.
She always cooked radish
and pork meatball soup.
Oh. I heard Ben talk about it.
That big mouth.
My retirement plan was to open a stall
next to his selling swamp eel.
He hated the idea.
Before he died, he mentioned the stall.
He wanted to talk to you about it.
I'm sure you invited me here
for more than small talk, right?
Word on the street is
you're planning to replace Thackery
as Ching He's new leader.
That true or not?
That information spread quickly.
So it appears San He knows
what's going on.
This is a big deal for us.
No matter who's chair.
If we have any issues now,
we'll be coming to Ching He for help.
Of course.
We each hold our positions.
As soon as we see an opportunity, shoot.
If one of us fails,
there'll still be a second chance.
I don't have a clear shot.
San He has always had
good relations with Ching He.
But remember, it was my father,
despite opposition, who fought for you.
You must recall all that.
Of course I do.
My brother respected your father.
He's in our hearts.
Then why were you unappreciative?
I recall how
you even conspired with Thackery
to accuse me of killing our own fixer.
I hope you don't plan to repeat that.
Put down the gun or I'll shoot.
You'll never kill her.
So this is San He showing its gratitude.
Huh. Now, just wait.
There's been a misunderstanding.
Hey, go check. Get down there.
Next time, come to my place.
It's safer there.
I'll leave them to catch up down there.
Damn. We won't get a chance
like that again. Fuck.
Sir Hong.
You're a traitor as well.
Here's to my succession.
Everything else, we've taken care of.
Thank you for your support.
And to your brother. For all his help.
Now everything's in place.
We're just waiting
on the succession ceremony.
Knowing Thackery as I do,
he won't comply so easily.
My concern is that once he gets out,
he'll give us trouble.
I would like to know
where that key was hidden.
Thackery's ring. That's his key.
It's just that the ring hasn't been found.
If Thackery hid it,
Sir Hong will know all there is to know.
As the most dangerous place is
often the safest,
I'd say it's in Ching He.
Your brother's been telling me
that you've helped him out a lot.
That's good.
You've finally come around.
Isn't this what you really wanted?
Tristan can finally carry on
the Hsueh family legacy for you.
I'm sure you know
a lot of people want
to use the Hsuehs to climb the ladder.
Or to take over from us.
Dad.
If Tristan takes the wrong path
to get to the top,
will you still support him?
I'm the one
who set your brother on this journey.
If he veers the wrong way,
then I have
to take responsibility for that.
Who's really in charge here?
We're all working for the Hsueh clan.
To look after our interests, sometimes
you have to get rid of a few obstacles.
It's for the greater good.
Louis.
I don't have long.
The path your brother takes,
that depends on your efforts.
It's all right, Dad.
Leave it to your sons. Get some rest.
INVITATION, CHING HE
FIXER CELESTIAL INAUGURATION
CELESTIAL, EARTH, SOLAR, LUNAR